<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gaming Tournament</string>
    <string name="title_ongoing">Ongoing</string>
    <string name="title_play">Play</string>
    <string name="title_result">Result</string>
    <string name="title_me">Me</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_earn">Earn</string>
    <string name="title_activity_match_detail">MatchDetailActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_result_detail">ResultDetailActivity</string>
    <string name="pubgRules">
•  No new PUBG Accouts Allowed. PUBG Accounts with Level less than 20 are not allowed to participate. Such participants will be kicked from the room and they will not be given refund.\n
•  If in anyway you fail to join the room by the match start time then we aren\'t responsible for it. Refund in such cases won\'t be processed. So make sure to join on time.\n
•  Do not share the Room ID and Password with anyone who has not joined the match. If you are found doing so, your account may get terminated and all the winnings will be lost. \n
•  Griefing and Teaming is against the game rules. Any participant found doing so will be disqualified and their prizes will be lost.\n
•  Room ID and Password will be shared in the app before 10 minutes of match start time.\n
•  Match will start after 10 minutes of Sharing Room ID and Password.\n
•  Make sure to grab ID and Password before the Match Start Time.\n
•  Make sure you join the Match Room ASAP, before the match starts.\n
•  This match is Paid match. To participate, you have to pay the entry fee amount. Join it before all the spots are filled.\n
•  Please note that the listed entry fee is per individual and not the squad/duo team. \n
•  Each member of a team (Squad or Duo) has to pay the entry fee and register individually for the match or tournament.\n
•  Once you join the match custom room, do not keep changing your position. If you do so, you may get kicked from the room.\n
•  Use only Mobile Device to Join Match. Do not use any Hacks or Emulators.\n
•  You will be also rewarded for each kill. Check the rewards details above.\n
•  Spots are given on the First Come First Basis.\n
•  Last standing man gets the Chicken Dinner Award.\n
•  If anyone found violating these rules then immediate action will be taken and respective accounts may get banned and rewards may be abandoned.\n
•  If you have any queries then contact us on lakshayofficialbusiness114@gmail.com \n
•  Also, if you want to arrange Giveaway or Sponsor any such match then drop us a mail at lakshayofficialbusiness114@gmail.com</string>


    <string name="aboutus_text">
        Gaming tournaments is an Ultimate Solution to all your eSports Games. \n \n

Gaming tournaments is an Online Portal which Offers Rewards and Unlimited Entertainment for Participating and Playing Games Online. Currently it supports some Popular and Trending Games i.e., PUBG Mobile, free fire , ludo and mini militia. \n \n

Founded and Launched on 25 april 2019 , was developed by a young mind from Delhi, India! \n \n

You might be addicted to PUBG Mobile , free fire , ludo and mini militia but just think what if you can start making money or living by Playing Mobile Games? Well, this is what Gaming tournaments Offers. Users can participate in the upcoming eSports games and Win Amazing Prizes and Rewards. \n \n

Currently, the platform has got support for \n
Ludo king, Mini militia , Free fire and PUBG Mobile, a Trending Game. Users can join Custom Rooms, and Get Rewards for Chicken Dinner and also for each Kill they Score. Sounds cool, huh?? Give it a try!
    </string>


    <!--Terms and conditions-->
    <string name="privacy_text">
        <b>Gaming tournaments built the gaming tournaments app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by Gaming tournaments at no cost and is intended for use as is.</b> \n \n

    This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service. \n \n

    If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. \n \n

    The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at Gaming tournaments unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy. \n \n

    Information Collection and Use \n
    For a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to Name, Email Address, Mobile Number, Instagram ID, Sex . The information that we request will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy. \n \n

    The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you. \n \n

    Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app \n \n

    Google Play Services \n
    AdMob \n
    Firebase Analytics \n
    Log Data \n
    We want to inform you that whenever you use our Service, in a case of an error in the app we collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing our Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics. \n \n

    Cookies \n
    Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your device\'s internal memory. \n \n

    This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collect information and improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service. \n \n

    Service Providers \n
    We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons: \n

    To facilitate our Service; \n
    To provide the Service on our behalf; \n \
    To perform Service-related services; or \n
    To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. \n
    We want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose. \n \n

    Security \n
    We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security. \n \n

    Links to Other Sites \n
    This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services. \n \n

    Children’s Privacy \n
    These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions. \n \n

    Changes to This Privacy Policy \n
    We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page. \n \n

    Contact Us \n
        If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.</string>

    <string name="refund_text">
        Our focus is complete customer satisfaction. In the event, if you are displeased with the services provided, we will refund back the money, provided the reasons are genuine and proved after investigation. Please read the fine prints of each deal before buying it, it provides all the details about the services or the product you purchase.\n\n

In case of dissatisfaction from our services, clients have the liberty to cancel their projects and request a refund from us. Our Policy for the cancellation and refund will be as follows: \n\n

        <b>CANCELLATION POLICY</b>\n\n

For Cancellations please contact the us via contact us link. \n\n

Requests received later than 1-2 business days prior to the end of the current service period will be treated as cancellation of services for the next service period.\n\n

        <b>REFUND POLICY</b> \n\n

We will try our best to create the suitable design concepts for our clients.

In case any client is not completely satisfied with our products we can provide a refund. 

If paid by credit card, refunds will be issued to the original credit card provided at the time of purchase and in case of payment gateway name payments refund will be made to the same account.
         
    </string>

    <string name="contact_text">Mr.Lakshay arora. (Grievance Officer)
www.gamingtournaments.com
Email: lakshayofficialbusiness114@gmail.com</string>

    <string name="tnc_text">
Your website may use the Terms and Conditions given below.
The terms "We" / "Us" / "Our"/”Company” individually and collectively refer to Gaming Tournament and the terms "Visitor” ”User” refer to the users.

This page states the Terms and Conditions under which you (Visitor) may visit this website (“www.gamingtournaments.in”)and app(gaming tournaments). Please read this page carefully. If you do not accept the Terms and Conditions stated here, we would request you to exit this site and app. The business, any of its business divisions and / or its subsidiaries, associate companies or subsidiaries to subsidiaries or such other investment companies (in India or abroad) reserve their respective rights to revise these Terms and Conditions at any time by updating this posting. You should visit this page periodically to re-appraise yourself of the Terms and Conditions, because they are binding on all users of this Website and app.

USE OF CONTENT

All logos, brands, marks headings, labels, names, signatures, numerals, shapes or any combinations thereof, appearing in this site, except as otherwise noted, are properties either owned, or used under licence, by the business and / or its associate entities who feature on this Website. The use of these properties or any other content on this site, except as provided in these terms and conditions or in the site content, is strictly prohibited.

You may not sell or modify the content of this Website  or reproduce, display, publicly perform, distribute, or otherwise use the materials in any way for any public or commercial purpose without the respective organisation’s or entity’s written permission.

ACCEPTABLE WEBSITE USE

(A) Security Rules
Visitors are prohibited from violating or attempting to violate the security of the Web site and app, including, without limitation, (1) accessing data not intended for such user or logging into a server or account which the user is not authorised to access, (2) attempting to probe, scan or test the vulnerability of a system or network or to breach security or authentication measures without proper authorisation, (3) attempting to interfere with service to any user, host or network, including, without limitation, via means of submitting a virus or "Trojan horse" to the Website, overloading, "flooding", "mail bombing" or "crashing", or (4) sending unsolicited electronic mail, including promotions and/or advertising of products or services. Violations of system or network security may result in civil or criminal liability. The business and / or its associate entities will have the right to investigate occurrences that they suspect as involving such violations and will have the right to involve, and cooperate with, law enforcement authorities in prosecuting users who are involved in such violations.

(B) General Rules
Visitors may not use the Web Site and app in order to transmit, distribute, store or destroy material (a) that could constitute or encourage conduct that would be considered a criminal offence or violate any applicable law or regulation, (b) in a manner that will infringe the copyright, trademark, trade secret or other intellectual property rights of others or violate the privacy or publicity of other personal rights of others, or © that is libellous, defamatory, pornographic, profane, obscene, threatening, abusive or hateful.

INDEMNITY

The User unilaterally agree to indemnify and hold harmless, without objection, the Company, its officers, directors, employees and agents from and against any claims, actions and/or demands and/or liabilities and/or losses and/or damages whatsoever arising from or resulting from their use of gamingtournaments.in or their breach of the terms .

LIABILITY

User agrees that neither Company nor its group companies, directors, officers or employee shall be liable for any direct or/and indirect or/and incidental or/and special or/and consequential or/and exemplary damages, resulting from the use or/and the inability to use the service or/and for cost of procurement of substitute goods or/and services or resulting from any goods or/and data or/and information or/and services purchased or/and obtained or/and messages received or/and transactions entered into through or/and from the service or/and resulting from unauthorized access to or/and alteration of user's transmissions or/and data or/and arising from any other matter relating to the service, including but not limited to, damages for loss of profits or/and use or/and data or other intangible, even if Company has been advised of the possibility of such damages.
User further agrees that Company shall not be liable for any damages arising from interruption, suspension or termination of service, including but not limited to direct or/and indirect or/and incidental or/and special consequential or/and exemplary damages, whether such interruption or/and suspension or/and termination was justified or not, negligent or intentional, inadvertent or advertent.
User agrees that Company shall not be responsible or liable to user, or anyone, for the statements or conduct of any third party of the service. In sum, in no event shall Company's total liability to the User for all damages or/and losses or/and causes of action exceed the amount paid by the User to Company, if any, that is related to the cause of action.

DISCLAIMER OF CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES

In no event shall Company or any parties, organizations or entities associated with the corporate brand name us or otherwise, mentioned at this Website be liable for any damages whatsoever (including, without limitations, incidental and consequential damages, lost profits, or damage to computer hardware or loss of data information or business interruption) resulting from the use or inability to use the Website and the Website material, whether based on warranty, contract, tort, or any other legal theory, and whether or not, such organization or entities were advised of the possibility of such damages.


    </string>
</resources>
